Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Mimi Benzell papers
1897-1972
1930-1972
Benzell, Mimi
03860
72.97 cubic feet (108 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
System Requirements
Mimi Benzell's musical recordings -- Audio tapes.
Luncheon with Mimi recordings -- Audio tapes.
Mimi Benzell's musical recordings -- Phonograph records -- 78 rpm.
Biography of Mimi Benzell
Mimi Benzell (1924-1972) was an American singer and radio talk show hostess during the twentieth century. Born in Bridgeport, Connecticut, Benzell started her show business career as a soprano opera singer and made a number of appearances with New York City's Metropolitan Opera Association during the 1940s. She moved into popular music in 1949 and enjoyed a long and notable career as a popular singer, giving numerous concert performances at night clubs and theaters between the late 1940s and 1960s and appearing in several musical theater productions, including the Broadway musical "Milk and Honey" (1961-1963) and the Off-Broadway plays "A Night on the Town" and "Show Boat". Benzell started singing in radio during the 1940s and made regular appearances on a number of popular radio shows during the 1950s, including "The Pet Milk Show" and "Railroad Hour" (1952-1954). Benzell also sang on a number of television shows during the 1950s a nd 1960s, including the "Mike Douglas Show" (1963). From 1964 to 1967, she was the hostess of WNBC New York's radio talk show "Luncheon with Mimi", in which she interviewed numerous celebrities, including Woody Allen and Nipsey Russell.
Scope and Content
Collection contains reel to reel audio tapes of Mimi Benzell's musical performances (including opera performances for the Metropolitan Opera Association, radio performances on "Radio Hour", and miscellaneous stage performances), reel to reel audio tapes of "Luncheon with Mimi", 78 rpm phonograph records of Benzell's musical performances (including opera performances for the Metropolitan Opera Association, radio performances on "Railroad Hour", and miscellaneous stage performances), and a few 33 rpm records of Benzell's musical performances (including "Milk and Honey"). Collection also contains original musical scores used by Benzell (including those for "Milk and Honey" and "A Night on the Town"), Benzell's radio show scripts (including those for "Railroad Hour" and "The Pet Milk Show"), a few 8 mm home movies (of Benzell, her family, and her travels), and a few 16 mm movies (of various Benzell performances), and reel to reel videotapes of Benzell's 1963 appearance on the "Mike Douglas Show". Collection also holds photographs and photograph negatives (of Benzell, her family, and show business colleagues), several scrapbooks created by Benzell, and a small amount of personal correspondence. A large amount of printed sheet music, clippings, programs and broadsides for Benzell performances, press releases, and miscellaneous printed materials are in this collection as well.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Mimi Benzell at the date of processing.
Additional Information
Partial finding aid available in repository.
Acquisition Information
The material was received from Walter Gould in 1972-1973 and 1979.
Access Terms
Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.); Women singers -- United States -- 20th century.; Opera -- United States -- 20th century.; Operas -- United States -- 20th century.; Musical theater -- United States -- 20th century.; Musicals -- United States -- 20th century.; Women in radio broadcasting -- United States -- 20th century.; Radio personalities -- United States -- 20th century.; Radio programs, Musical -- United States -- 20th century.; Radio talk shows -- United States -- 20th century.;; Audiotapes.; Phonograph records.; Scores.; Scrapbooks.;; Luncheon with Mimi (Radio program); Railroad hour (Radio program)
Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences; Music; Performing Arts; Women
Container List
- Sound Tapes (7 inch reel, 1200 feet):
  - Benzell, Mimi - singing opera, undated (Box 1)
  - Benzell, Mimi - singing popular songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Introductions by Mimi (practice tape), undated (Box 1)
  - Brown, Jimmy - Actor, undated (Box 1)
  - Bull fight (two tapes), undated (Box 1)
  - Cardiff, Jack - Movie director, undated (Box 1)
  - Carston, Peter - Actor, undated (Box 1)
  - Christie, Julie - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - Clark, Ossie and Pollack, Alice - Store clerks, undated (Box 1)
  - Commercials - Coca Cola and Libby, undated (Box 1)
  - Despax, Oliver - Actor, undated (Box 1)
  - Conklin, Roger - Manager "Soaquarium, Miami, Florida" (two tapes), undated (Box 1)
  - Demming, Vaugh - Stuntman, undated (Box 1)
  - Devize, England - various citizens of town, undated (Box 1)
  - Devize market - various citizens of town, undated (Box 1)
  - Elias, Louis - Stunt double, undated (Box 1)
  - England, George - Producer (two tapes), undated (Box 1)
  - Grayson, Kathryn - Singer, undated (Box 1)
  - Harrod's Department Store - various employees (two tapes), undated (Box 1)
  - Jaffey, Irving - Ice skater, undated (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Patricia - Kathryn Grayson's daughter, undated (Box 1)
  - Kyako, Kishida - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - Lisi, Virna - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - "Lord Jim" preview (two tapes, two copies of reel two), undated (Box 1)
  - Mimieux, Yvette - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - O'Brian, Hugh - Actor, undated (Box 1)
  - Puiver, Kurt - Ice skater, undated (Box 1)
  - Raphael, Frederic - Director, undated (Box 1)
  - Silverman, Ernest - Café owner, undated (Box 1)
  - Stauffer, Teddy - Hotel manager, undated (Box 1)
  - Sternfield, Aaron - Actor, undated (Box 1)
  - Taylor, Rod - Actor (two tapes), undated (Box 1)
  - Torna, Regina - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - Walker, Fiona - Actress, undated (Box 1)
  - Woodworth, Constance - ?, undated (Box 1)
  - Schaap, Dick - Author, 03/29, no year (Box 17)
  - Brothers, Joyce - Psychologist, 03/29, no year (Box 17)
  - Sutter, Linda - subsituting for Mimi, 03/29, no year (Box 17)
  - Rosten, Leo - Author, 09/02, no year (Box 17)
  - Gavin, John - Actor, 09/02, no year (Box 17)
  - Crandall, Brad - substituting for Mimi, 09/02, no year (Box 17)
  - Acapulco - Description of place, 11/20, no year (Box 1)
  - Roman, Carlos - Cliff diver, 1964 (Box 1)
  - DeLeon, Miguel - Taxi driver, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Julie - Actress, 01/07/1964 (Box 1)
  - Moore, Sonja - Actress, 01/07/1964 (Box 1)
  - Wassenman, Robert - Handwriting analyst, 01/07/1964 (Box 1)
  - Knight, Felix - Opera singer, 04/16/1964 (Box 1)
  - Murray, Katherine - Dancer, 04/16/1964 (Box 1)
  - Thomas, Frank - Baseball player, 04/16/1964 (Box 1)
  - Taylor, Elaine - Kelly Girl, 04/20/1964 (Box 1)
  - Howard, Esther - Volunteer worker for National Jewish Hospital, Denver, Colorado, 04/20/1964 (Box 1)
  - Yssel, Gus - President, Rockefeller Center, 04/20/1964 (Box 1)
  - Small, Gertrude - Stockbroker, 04/21/1964 (Box 1)
  - Lowe, Janet - Stockbroker, 04/21/1964 (Box 1)
  - Darvis, Nickie - Dancer and author, 04/21/1964 (Box 1)
  - Reels 1 and 2 concerning speeches from Mayor Wagner and President Lyndon B. Johnson concerning the New York World's Fair opening, 04/22/1964 (Box 1)
  - Hildegard - Entertainer, 04/22/1964 (Box 1)
  - Flamm, Donald - Broadcaster, 04/22/1964 (Box 1)
  - Tucker, Sophie - Singer, 04/23/1964 (Box 1)
  - Gardner, Ily - Columnist, 04/23/1964 (Box 1)
  - Pflaninger, Sylvia - Author, 04/24/1964 (Box 1)
  - Bean, Orsen - TV panelist, 04/24/1964 (Box 1)
  - Wolcott, Charles C. - Educator, 04/24/1964 (Box 1)
  - Daniel, Margaret Truman - President Truman's daughter, 04/28/1964 (Box 2)
  - French, Eleanor Clark - New York City Commissioner to United Nations, 04/28/1964 (Box 2)
  - Nickerson, Eugene - Nassau County Executive, 04/29/1964 (Box 2)
  - Atlas, Sol G. - Real estate developer, 04/29/1964 (Box 2)
  - Dunbar, Ernest - Editor, LOOK Magazine, 04/30/1964 (Box 2)
  - Kaner, Walter - Columnist, 04/30/1964 (Box 2)
  - Leslie, Warren - Author, 05/01/1964 (Box 2)
  - Cambridge, Godfrey - Comedian, 05/01/1964 (Box 2)
  - Cambridge, Barbara (Mrs. Godfrey) - Actress, 05/01/1964 (Box 2)
  - House, Sally Ann - Musical comedy star, 05/04/1964 (Box 2)
  - Diseaux, Nancy - Musical comedy star, 05/04/1964 (Box 2)
  - Morran, Jim - Publisher, 05/04/1964 (Box 2)
  - Bard, Jan - Songwriter, 05/05/1964 (Box 2)
  - Schaeffer, George - Producer-director, 05/05/1964 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Florence - Executive Director, Louise Weiss Service, 05/06/1964 (Box 2)
  - Griffin, Merv - Television celebrity, 05/06/1964 (Box 2)
  - Stein, Robert - Editor, Redbook, 05/06/1964 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, Nancy - Singer, 05/07/1964 (Box 2)
  - Duddly, Lynn -Night club act writer, 05/07/1964 (Box 2)
  - Kaufmann, William - Writer, 05/06/1964 (Box 2)
  - Lindfors, Viveca - Actress, 05/06/1964 (Box 2)
  - Jarvis, Lucy - NBC Television producer, 05/11/1964 (Box 2)
  - Bogomolovia, Nina - Member, Soviet Women's Committee, and author, 05/11/1964 (Box 2)
  - Henderson, Skitch - Musician, 05/12/1964 (Box 2)
  - Burns, John J. - Commisioner, New York State government, 05/12/1964 (Box 2)
  - Shang, Fred - Director, 05/13/1964 (Box 3)
  - Ellison, Charles - Director, Offive of Cultural Presentation, Washington, D.C., 05/13/1964 (Box 3)
  - Purcell, Ed - Program Officer, Inter-American Programs, Washington, D.C., 05/13/1964 (Box 3)
  - Pollak, Mrs. Sidney - Administrative Director Jewish Guild of the Blind, 05/14/1964 (Box 3)
  - Riley, Charles Nelson - Musical star, 05/14/1964 (Box 3)
  - Bekkel, Theodore - Actor, 05/15/1964 (Box 3)
  - Abel, Allan - Observer, 05/15/1964 (Box 3)
  - Wright, Marlon - NAACP counselor, 05/18/1964 (Box 3)
  - Whitmore, James - Actor, 05/18/1964 (Box 3)
  - Hamlin, Oscar - History professor, Harvard, 05/18/1964 (Box 3)
  - Vanderherval, William - Special Assistant to Attorney General Robert Kennedy, 05/19/1964 (Box 3)
  - Tuckman, Mrs. Kate - Principal, School #184, Manhattan, 05/19/1964 (Box 3)
  - Ford, Paul - Actor, 05/19/1964 (Box 3)
  - Fields, Totie - Comedienne, 05/20/1964 (Box 3)
  - Sobel, Louis - Columnist, 05/20/1964 (Box 3)
  - Wheatly, Joanne - Singer, 05/21/1964 (Box 3)
  - Kanner, Hal - Singer, 05/21/1964 (Box 3)
  - Allen, Mel - Broadcaster, 05/21/1964 (Box 3)
  - Glenwille, Peter - Director, 05/22/1964 (Box 3)
  - Carmell, Eddie - Comic, 05/22/1964 (Box 3)
  - Bytoni, Giovani - Pasta merchant, 05/25/1964 (Box 3)
  - Peters, Gorald - Radio performer, 05/25/1964 (Box 3)
  - Goulet, Robert - Singer, 05/25/1964 (Box 3)
  - Belinki, Helen - Cookbook author, 05/25/1964 (Box 3)
  - Jones, Candy - Model, 05/26/1964 (Box 3)
  - Schultz, Hildegard - German radio producer, 05/26/1964 (Box 3)
  - Case, Allan - Television actor, 05/26/1964 (Box 3)
  - Feeley, Mary - Money management consultant, 05/27/1964 (Box 3)
  - Gregory, Dick - Comedian, 05/27/1964 (Box 3)
  - O'Sullivan, Maureen - Actress, 05/28/1964 (Box 3)
  - Gary, Harold - Actor, 05/28/1964 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Steven - J.F. Kennedy Library press agent, 05/28/1964 (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Earl - Columnist, 05/29/1964 (Box 4)
  - Adler, Ernest - Hairdresser, 05/29/1964 (Box 4)
  - Kitt, Ertha - Singer, 06/01/1964 (Box 4)
  - Douglas, Jack - Author, 06/01/1964 (Box 4)
  - Graham, Virginia - TV Moderator, 06/02/1964 (Box 4)
  - Ponds, Helaine - Costumer, 06/02/1964 (Box 4)
  - Mansfield, Jane - Actress, 06/03/1964 (Box 4)
  - Haggerty, Mickie - Promoter, 06/03/1964 (Box 4)
  - Orbin, Robert - Comedy writer, 06/03/1964 (Box 4)
  - Klepper, Mike - Director-producer, 06/03/1964 (Box 4)
  - DeHavilland, Olivia - Actress, 06/04/1964 (Box 4)
  - Brandon, Johnnie - Composer, 06/04/1964 (Box 4)
  - Levinson, Sam - Humorist, 06/05/1964 (Box 4)
  - Olson, Robert - Director, Boys Club of New York, 06/05/1964 (Box 4)
  - Dessau, Axel - Director, Danish travel office, 06/05/1964 (Box 4)
  - Rifter, Carolyne - Comedienne, 06/08/1964 (Box 4)
  - Dowel, Gorvey - Writer, 06/08/1964 (Box 4)
  - Klienholtz, Frank - Art critic, 06/08/1964 (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Florence - Actress, 06/09/1964 (Box 4)
  - Liberace - Pianist, 06/09/1964 (Box 4)
  - Carren, Joan - Actress, 06/09/1964 (Box 4)
  - Checkers, Chubby - Entertainer, 06/10/1964 (Box 4)
  - Grossman, Ruth - Cookbook author, 06/10/1964 (Box 4)
  - Grossman, Bob - Cookbook author, 06/10/1964 (Box 4)
  - Britton, Sherry - Singer, 06/11/1964 (Box 4)
  - DeCosta, Morton - Director, 06/11/1964 (Box 4)
  - King, Lila - Press agent, 06/12/1964 (Box 4)
  - Schacht, Al - "Clown prince of baseball", 06/12/1964 (Box 4)
  - Jones, Candy - substitute for Mimi, 06/16/1964 (Box 5)
  - Burroughs, Abe - Playwright, 06/16/1964 (Box 5)
  - Greene, Adolph - Playwright, 06/16/1964 (Box 5)
  - Avalon, Frankie - Singer, 06/16/1964 (Box 5)
  - Franzblau, Rose - Psychologist, 06/17/1964 (Box 5)
  - Strong, Marrianne - Society publicist, 06/17/1964 (Box 5)
  - Thompson, Edward - New York City Fire Commisioner, 06/18/1964 (Box 5)
  - Swing, Raymond - Broadcaster-writer, 06/18/1964 (Box 5)
  - Unidentified, could not get correct speed, marked "Take It Jack Cassidy", 06/19/1964 (Box 5)
  - Carroll, Bob - Actor, 06/19/1964 (Box 5)
  - Cassidy, Jack - Actor, 06/19/1964 (Box 5)
  - Simms, Sylvia - Songstress, 06/22/1964 (Box 5)
  - Johnson, Van - Actor, 06/22/1964 (Box 5)
  - Chadwick, Florence - Swimmer, 06/23/1964 (Box 5)
  - Nixon, Marni - Actress, 06/23/1964 (Box 5)
  - Gold, Ernest - Composer, 06/23/1964 (Box 5)
  - Sahl, Mort - Comedian, 06/24/1964 (Box 5)
  - Benton, Robert - Art editor, 06/24/1964 (Box 5)
  - Newman, David - Freelance writer, 06/24/1964 (Box 5)
  - Russell, Anna - Actress, 06/25/1964 (Box 5)
  - Buttons, Dick - Ice skater, 06/25/1964 (Box 5)
  - Cook, Sam - Writer, 06/26/1964 (Box 5)
  - Michaels, Sydney - Writer, 06/26/1964 (Box 5)
  - Downs, Hugh - TV moderator, 06/29/1964 (Box 5)
  - Dailey, Irene - Actress, 06/29/1964 (Box 5)
  - Funicello, Annette - Singer/actress, 06/30/1964 (Box 5)
  - LaRosa, Julius - Singer/actor, 06/30/1964 (Box 5)
  - Kallen, Kitty - Musical recording star, 07/01/1964 (Box 6)
  - Wagner, Roger - Musical director, 07/01/1964 (Box 6)
  - Tapes marked "Short day due to special broadcast", 07/01/1964 (Box 6)
  - Russell, Nipsey - Actor, 07/02/1964 (Box 6)
  - DeSilva, Howard - Actor/director, 07/02/1964 (Box 6)
  - Knight, Felix - Singer, 07/02/1964 (Box 6)
  - VanVorn, Monique - Singer, 07/03/1964 (Box 6)
  - Janney, Leon - Actor, 07/03/1964 (Box 6)
  - White, Bob - Writer, 07/03/1964 (Box 6)
  - McDowell, Roddey - Actor, 07/06/1964 (Box 6)
  - Maccard, Jan - Actress, 07/06/1964 (Box 6)
  - Elangas, Dorothy - New York City Beauty Contest winner, 07/06/1964 (Box 6)
  - Burman, Shelly - Comedian, 07/06/1964 (Box 6)
  - McDowall, Roddy - Actor, 07/07/1964 (Box 6)
  - 1964 All Star Basketball game and sports casting, 07/07/1964 (Box 6)
  - Clarey, Robert - Musical producer, 07/08/1964 (Box 6)
  - Sheer, Jerry - Vice-president, department store, 07/08/1964 (Box 6)
  - Page, Geraldine - Actress, 07/09/1964 (Box 6)
  - Blackwell, Earl - Celebrity Service manager, 07/09/1964 (Box 6)
  - Grossinger, Jennie - Hostess, Grossinger Hotel, 07/10/1964 (Box 6)
  - Lopez, Vincent - Musician, 07/10/1964 (Box 6)
  - Goldwater, Barry - Senator (political speech, not interview), 07/10/1964 (Box 6)
  - Lombardo, Guy - Entertainer, orchestra leader, 07/13/1964 (Box 6)
  - Berthelson, Larry - Puppeteer, 07/14/1964 (Box 6)
  - Porter, Don - Actor, 07/14/1964 (Box 6)
  - Prince, Hal - Producer, 07/17/1964 (Box 6)
  - Braenard, Frank - Director of Operation Sailing Ships, 07/17/1964 (Box 6)
  - Skinner, Cornelius Otis - Author, 07/20/1964 (Box 6)
  - Lind, Gloria - Recording star, 07/20/1964 (Box 6)
  - Scott, Martha - Actress, 07/15/1964 (Box 7)
  - Neuta, Benevada - Actress, 07/15/1964 (Box 7)
  - Allen, Woody - Comedian, 07/16/1964 (Box 7)
  - Susan, Jacqualine - Actress, 07/16/1964 (Box 7)
  - Meader, Vaughn - Recording star, 07/21/1964 (Box 7)
  - Hunter, Kim - Actress, 07/21/1964 (Box 7)
  - Neumann, Vera - Artist-designer, 07/22/1964 (Box 7)
  - Vernon, Jackie - Comedian, 07/22/1964 (Box 7)
  - Willson, Meredith - Composer, 07/23/1964 (Box 7)
  - Willson, Rene - Mrs. Meredith Willson, 07/23/1964 (Box 7)
  - Ireland, John - Actor, 07/23/1964 (Box 7)
  - Boschard, Helen - Chairman, Childrens Entertainment Center, 07/24/1964 (Box 7)
  - O'Keefe, Dennis - Actor, 07/24/1964 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Robert - Actor, 07/27/1964 (Box 7)
  - Ulmanvoski, Alexander - Student-social worker, 07/27/1964 (Box 7)
  - Blighton, Larry - Actor, 07/28/1964 (Box 7)
  - Nero, Peter - Musician, 07/28/1964 (Box 7)
  - Hayes, Richard - Singer-actor, 07/29/1964 (Box 7)
  - Hamilton, Mrs. Cena - President, Gulliver Trails, Children's Camp agency, 07/29/1964 (Box 7)
  - Gunti, Morty - Comedian, 08/03/1964 (Box 7)
  - Panella, Candy - Fashion editor, 08/03/1964 (Box 7)
  - Knight, Ethel Bloom (Mrs. Felix) - Child radio star, 08/04/1964 (Box 7)
  - Diller, Phyllis - Comedienne, 08/04/1964 (Box 7)
  - Pruden, Bonnie - President, Institute of Physical Fitness, 08/05/1964 (Box 8)
  - Crown, Al - Producer, 08/05/1964 (Box 8)
  - Ballin, Ina - Actress, 08/06/1964 (Box 8)
  - Stein, Phil - Manager-producer, 08/06/1964 (Box 8)
  - Mobray, Allan - Actor, 08/07/1964 (Box 8)
  - Meehan, Danny - Actor, 08/07/1964 (Box 8)
  - Parkins, Molly - Actress, 08/08/1964 (Box 8)
  - Mackeehan, Ann - World's Fair Queen, 08/10/1964 (Box 8)
  - Yule, Mrs. Tom (Marjorie) - Actor's Wife, 08/10/1964 (Box 8)
  - Cahn, Sammy - Lyric songwriter, 08/10/1964 (Box 8)
  - Fuchsberg, Jack - Lawyer, 08/11/1964 (Box 8)
  - Schenzen, Walter - Producer, 08/11/1964 (Box 8)
  - Benzell Promos, 08/12/1964 (Box 8)
  - Warfield, William - Singer, 08/12/1964 (Box 8)
  - Taylor, Rene - Actress-comedienne, 08/12/1964 (Box 8)
  - DuPoir, Leonard - Conductor, 08/14/1964 (Box 8)
  - Hickman, Darryl - Actor, 08/14/1964 (Box 8)
  - Markell, William - Medical doctor, 08/18/1964 (Box 8)
  - Ross, Lynn - College student, fashion designer, 08/18/1964 (Box 8)
  - Piatza, Ben - Actor, 08/19/1964 (Box 8)
  - Seagler, Sylvia - Bus-line director, 08/19/1964 (Box 8)
  - Sinatra, Frank Jr. - Singer, 08/21/1964 (Box 8)
  - Freeman, Al - Actor, 08/21/1964 (Box 8)
  - Dee, Ruby - Actress, 08/24/1964 (Box 8)
  - Daner, Barbara - Actress (Mrs. Allen Arkan), 08/24/1964 (Box 8)
  - Arkan, Allen - Actor, 08/24/1964 (Box 8)
  - Wyler, Gretchen - Dancer, 08/25/1964 (Box 9)
  - Wood, Evelyn - Founder of Reading Dynamics, 08/25/19664 (Box 9)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Alice - Magazine editor, 08/26/1964 (Box 9)
  - Davis, Ossie - Actor, 08/26/1964 (Box 9)
  - Bruce, Judt - Actress, 08/27/1964 (Box 9)
  - Kasznar, Kurt - Actor, 08/27/1964 (Box 9)
  - Kean, Betty - Comedienne, 08/28/1964 (Box 9)
  - Parker, Lew - Actor, 08/28/1964 (Box 9)
  - Erskine, Howard - Producer, 08/28/1964 (Box 9)
  - Berry, Clair - Singer (sister team), 08/31/1964 (Box 9)
  - Berry, Myrna - Singer (sister team), 08/31/1964 (Box 9)
  - Carson, Mindy - Singer-actress, 09/01/1964 (Box 9)
  - Landau, Jack - Producer, 09/01/1964 (Box 9)
  - Lesculie, Jack - TV announcer, 09/02/1964 (Box 9)
  - Davidson, Muriel - Magazine writer, 09/02/1964 (Box 9)
  - Brown, Helen Gurley - Author, 09/03/1964 (Box 9)
  - McMahon, Ed - TV announcer, 09/03/1964 (Box 9)
  - Winters, Shelly - Actress, 09/04/1964 (Box 9)
  - Hayden, Melisa - Ballerina, 09/04/1964 (Box 9)
  - Chapin, Scarlet - Producer, 09/04/1964 (Box 9)
  - Evans, Lee - Pianist, 09/07/1964 (Box 9)
  - Cantelli, Polly - Fashion director, 09/07/1964 (Box 9)
  - Kramer, Walt - Producer, 09/08/1964 (Box 9)
  - Kiley, Richard - Actor, 09/08/1964 (Box 9)
  - Landon, Michael - Actor, 09/09/1964 (Box 10)
  - Hoffeld, Bill - Interior designer, 09/09/1964 (Box 10)
  - Young, Gig - Actor, 09/10/1964 (Box 10)
  - Spitzer, Murry - Business man, 09/10/1964 (Box 10)
  - O'Neal, Patrick - Actor, 09/11/1964 (Box 10)
  - Gordon, Dorothy - TV moderator, 09/11/1964 (Box 10)
  - Parker, Fess - Actor, 09/14/1964 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Myran - Comedian, 09/14/1964 (Box 10)
  - Victor, Sally - Hat designer, 09/15/1964 (Box 10)
  - Sidney, Sylvia - Actress, 09/15/1964 (Box 10)
  - Albertson, Jack - Actor, 09/16/1964 (Box 10)
  - Montague, Lord Buela - English nobleman, 09/16/1964 (Box 10)
  - Jackson, Anne - Actress, 09/17/1964 (Box 10)
  - Wallach, Eli - Actor, 09/17/1964 (Box 10)
  - Hill, Lucian - Translator, 09/17/1964 (Box 10)
  - Haverly, John P. - Monsignor and educator, 09/18/1964 (Box 10)
  - Blackshaw, Kenneth - New York World's Fair Manager, 09/18/1964 (Box 10)
  - Monroe, Vaughn - Singer, 09/21/1964 (Box 10)
  - Stearn, Michael - War correspondant, 09/21/1964 (Box 10)
  - Kantor, Arthur - Press agent, 09/22/1964 (Box 10)
  - Israel, Leonard - Business man, 09/22/1964 (Box 10)
  - Gazzara, Ben - Actor, 09/22/1964 (Box 10)
  - Jaffe, Sam - Actor, 09/24/1964 (Box 10)
  - Ackerman, Betty - Actress, 09/24/1964 (Box 10)
  - Hoffman, Jay - Musician, 09/25/1964 (Box 11)
  - Bloom, Claire - Actress, 09/25/1964 (Box 11)
  - O'Fallan, Shawn - Author, 09/291964 (Box 11)
  - Gaussman, Victoria - Actor, 09/29/1964 (Box 11)
  - Hammer, Victor - President, Hammer Galleries, 09/30/1964 (Box 11)
  - Conley, Joe - Producer, 09/30/1964 (Box 11)
  - McLoughan, Mary Ann - Physical fitness advocate, 10/01/1964 (Box 11)
  - Rossin, Robert - Producer, 10/01/1964 (Box 11)
  - Bogan, Sylvia - Financial consultant, 10/09/1964 (Box 11)
  - Shouggler, Goodrich - University professor, 10/09/1964 (Box 11)
  - Rude, Beth - Chaplin, Ship "University Seven Seas", 10/12/1964 (Box 11)
  - Tuttle, William - Movie make-up artist, 10/13/1964 (Box 11)
  - Perkins, Marlin - Zoo director, 10/13/1964 (Box 11)
  - Fowler, Jim - Falconist, 10/13/1964 (Box 11)
  - Cass, Peggy - Singer, 10/14/1964 (Box 11)
  - Peckham, Ted - Antique dealer, 10/14/1964 (Box 11)
  - Rollenstein, Alfred - Music director, 10/19/1964 (Box 11)
  - Spinetti, Victor - Actor, 10/19/1964 (Box 11)
  - House, Sally Ann - Actress, 10/20/1964 (Box 11)
  - Ralston, Ray - Actor, 10/20/1964 (Box 11)
  - McPortland, Mary Ann - Pianist, 10/21/1964 (Box 11)
  - Massey, Raymond - Actor, 10/21/1964 (Box 11)
  - Hayber, Bill - Auctioneer, 10/22/1964 (Box 11)
  - Hayes, Helen - Actress, 10/22/1964 (Box 11)
  - Kaupman, Rosamand - Writer, 10/23/1964 (Box 12)
  - Lane, Lydia - Columnist, 10/23/1964 (Box 12)
  - Galeb, Pat - Corportate President, 10/23/1964 (Box 12)
  - King, Alan - Comedian, 10/26/1964 (Box 12)
  - Goldfater, Edward - Corporate President, 10/26/1964 (Box 12)
  - Louch, Jean - Public relations consultant, 10/27/1964 (Box 12)
  - Casanni, Egor - Publisher, 10/27/1964 (Box 12)
  - Champaign, Marion - Lawyer-writer, 10/28/1964 (Box 12)
  - German, James - Medical doctor, 10/28/1964 (Box 12)
  - Rossburough, Jean - Director, New York Chapter National Foundation March of Dimes, 10/28/1964 (Box 12)
  - Leake, Sybil - ESP expert and author, 10/29/1964 (Box 12)
  - Leavarrie, Lorrenzo - Singer, 10/29/1964 (Box 12)
  - Rathbone, Julia - Granddaughter of a prominent actor, 10/30/1964 (Box 12)
  - Raine, Jessica - Granddaughter of a prominent actor, 10/30/1964 (Box 12)
  - Komer, Jill - Granddaughter of a prominent actor, 10/30/1964 (Box 12)
  - Foster, Stephanie - Granddaughter of a prominent actor, 10/30/1964 (Box 12)
  - Uggams, Leslie - Singer, 11/02/1964 (Box 12)
  - Berquist, Laura - Writer, 11/02/1964 (Box 12)
  - McGinnis, Helen - Writer, 11/03/1964 (Box 12)
  - Pierre Amant, John - Actor, 11/03/1964 (Box 12)
  - Goldwater, Barry - Senator, political speech, not interview, 11/04/1964 (Box 12)
  - Steindler, Paul - Café owner, 11/04/1964 (Box 12)
  - Wilson, Julie - Singer, 11/04/1964 (Box 12)
  - Alexander, Joan - Actress, 11/05/1964 (Box 12)
  - Bacharrach, Burt - Columnist, 11/05/1964 (Box 12)